所以我多次提到语义 HTML 一词
So I mentioned the term semantic HTML a couple of times
在这个部分。
in this section.
所以现在让我们实际上非常快速地定义我
And so let's now actually very quickly define what I
实际上是指语义HTML。
actually mean by semantic HTML.
所以在 HTML 中，当我们谈论语义时，
So in HTML, when we talk about semantics,
我们的意思是某些元素实际上有
what we mean is that certain elements have actually
赋予它们的意义或目的。
a meaning or a purpose attached to them.
因此，当我们考虑某个 HTML 元素时，
So when we think about a certain HTML element,
我们实际上不应该考虑该元素的外观
we should actually not think about what that element looks
就像它在页面上呈现的那样。
like as it's rendered on the page.
但相反，我们应该考虑那个元素
But instead we should think about what that element
实际上意味着什么以及它代表什么。
actually means and what it stands for.
所以这基本上是语义 HTML 的定义。
So that is basically the definition of semantic HTML.
现在，并非 HTML 中的所有元素都是语义的。
Now, not all elements in HTML are semantic.
实际上我之前谈过一点
And actually I talked a little bit about that before
在这个元素中。所以强元素，
here in this element. So the strong element,
这使得我们的元素在页面上看起来很粗。
which makes our element look bold here on the page.
所以请记住我之前是如何使用 B 元素的，
So remember how previously I used the B element,
它只是将其内容变为粗体，
which simply turns its content bold,
但没有附加任何意义。对？
but doesn't attach it any meaning. Right?
所以我之前解释过。
So I explained that before.
所以现在也许它更有意义了。
And so now maybe it makes a bit more sense.
再次，通过在这里使用强元素，
So again, by using the strong element here,
文本在浏览器中仍会显示为粗体，
the text will still look bold here in the browser,
但这里真正重要的是我们现在分配一些
but what really matters here is that we now assign some
这里的内容的意思。
meaning to this content here.
我们现在说这是一个强大的内容，
We now say that is a strong content,
这基本上意味着一个非常重要的内容和
which means basically a very important piece of content and
这件作品也一样。所以这个基本词在这里。
the same here for this piece. So this fundamental word here.
因此，我们再次使用 EM 来强调这一点。
So again, we use EM for emphasizing this.
所以它在网页上看起来仍然是 atelic，
And so it still looks atelic here on the webpage,
但我们真正的意思是我们强调了这个词
but what we really mean is that we emphasized this word
这里。所以我们特别强调了它，是的，
here. So we gave it a special emphasis and yeah,
这就是这个元素现在的意思。
that's what this element here right now means.
好的，实际上也是如此
Okay, and the same is actually true for
我们在上一个视频中使用的所有这些元素。
all of these elements that we used in the last video.
所以例如这里，这个导航元素，
So for example here, this navigation element,
这一切都是为了创造一个盒子，
all this does is to create a box,
记住其中包含这四个锚元素，
remember which then contains these four anchor elements,
但在视觉上它并没有真正做任何事情。
but visually it doesn't really do anything.
这一切都是为了表达一种意义
All this does is to represent as a meaning
这是一个导航，但不是使用导航，
that this is a navigation, but instead of using nav,
我们也可以使用更通用的元素，
we could also have used a more generic element,
这是 div 元素。
which is the div element.
例如， div 在这里打开和关闭它，然后再一次，
So for example, div open and close it here, and again,
视觉上什么都不会改变。
visually nothing will change.
所以这一切都是为了创造一个新的盒子，
And so all this did was to create a new box,
但这个盒子没有任何意义。
but the box without any meaning.
这就是 div 的含义。
So that's what div stands for.
所以回到 HTML 5 之前的一天，
So back in the day before HTML five,
我们总是为我们需要的每个盒子使用 div
we always use divs for every single box that we needed
像这样在页面上，
like this on the page,
但后来 HTML 5 出现并引入了这个概念
but then HTML five came around and introduced this concept
语义 HTML。
of semantic HTML.
所以现在我们应该只在不使用的时候使用 div 元素
And so now we should only use the div element when we don't
想给某个容器附加某种意义。
want to attach a certain meaning to a certain container.
所以到我们页面上的某个like box元素。
So to a certain like box element on our page.
所以在这种情况下，
So in this case,
我们真的希望这意味着它是一个导航。
we really want this to mean that it's a navigation.
所以我们为此使用导航元素。
And so we use the navigation element for that.
好的。文章的标题也是如此，
Okay. And the same is true for the article, the header,
我们在这里的页脚。
the footer that we have down here.
事实上，即使对于段落也是如此，
And in fact it is true even for the paragraph,
例如，因为所有这些，65
for example, because all that,
这里的这一段和所有其他的段落真的是，
this paragraph here and all the other paragraphs really are,
本质上是填充文本的框。
are essentially boxes filled with text.
现在 P 当然确实有语义。
Now the P of course does have a semantic meaning.
这意味着它是一个段落，
It means that it is a paragraph,
但我们可以再次使用没有任何意义的通用框。
but we could again use a generic box without any meaning.
所以 div 和任何东西都不会在视觉上发生变化。
So the div and nothing would change visually.
好的。实际上，这里确实发生了一些变化。
Okay. Actually something did change here.
所以我们失去了一些空白
So we lost some of the white space that
我们确实在P附近。
we do have around the P.
好吧，还是把它放回这里吧
All right, so let's put it back here anyway
到 P 是因为我们希望它具有某种意义。
to the P because we want it to have some meaning.
当然我们也想要浏览器的间距
And of course we also want the spacing that's the browser
默认情况下，我们围绕 P 元素。
gives us by default around the P elements.
现在好了，但我提到的想法仍然成立
Now okay, but the idea that I mentioned still holds
因为我们可以很容易地在这里重建这个空间
because we could very easily recreate this space here
稍后使用一些 CSS。
using some CSS later.
所以如果我们想要，
So if we wanted,
事实上，我们可以只用 div 构建整个网页
we could in fact build the entire webpage only out of div
如果我们想要元素
elements if we wanted and
然后使用 CSS 为它们设置我们想要的样式。
then use CSS to style them as we want.
但我们当然不会那样做。
But of course we don't do that.
我们使用语义 HTML 来赋予四个元素含义。
We use semantic HTML to give four elements meaning.
现在你可能会问我们为什么要这么做
Now you might ask why we actually do that
并且有多种原因。
and there are multiple reasons.
实际上，我想我已经提到过它们。
And I think I mentioned them already, actually.
所以其中之一是搜索引擎优化，
So one of them is a search engine optimization,
这基本上意味着像谷歌这样的搜索引擎
which basically means that a search engine such as Google
将能够理解您的内容的结构。
will be able to understand the structure of your content.
因此他们将能够更好地分析
And therefore they will be better able to analyze
您的内容和网页的全部内容。
what your content and what your webpage is all about.
同样，编写语义 HTML 对于
Also writing semantic HTML is extremely important for
可访问性，尤其是对于人们
accessibility and especially for people
依靠屏幕阅读器在网页上消费的人。
who rely on screen readers to consume on web pages.
好的，所以我希望这是有道理的，
Okay, so I hope that this makes sense,
我们也会继续探讨这个话题
and we will also keep touching on the subject
当我们完成剩下的课程时，
as we go through the rest of the course,
但我仍然想从很
but I still wanted to make it very clear from the very
当我们想到 HTML 时，
beginning that when we think about HTML,
我们不应该只考虑它的实际外观
we should not only think about how it actually looks like
在浏览器中，
in the browser,
但更多的是关于这些元素的实际含义
but even more about what these elements actually mean
以及他们代表什么。
and what they stand for.
话虽如此，
And with that being said,
我们已经完成了本节中必须学习的所有内容。
we kind of finished all we had to learn in this section.
所以在下一个视频中，
And so in the next video,
我们将配置 vs 代码多一点，
we will configure vs code a little bit more,
然后我们将继续进行最后两个挑战
and then we will move on to two final challenges
在节中。
in the section.
所以不要等待，让我们继续这里的下一个讲座。
So don't wait and let's move on to the next lecture here.